<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Guides and tips for Pokemon Go</string>
    <string name="s1_title">How to play Pokémon Go?</string>
    <string name="s1_subtitle">Pokémon Go retains the basics of Pokémon games past — catching Pokémon, battling at Gyms, using ...</string>
    <string name="s2_title">How to download and play Pokemon Go right now?</string>
    <string name="s2_subtitle">If you want to play Pokémon Go on your device, and you\'re not in a country that has made Pokémon Go available...</string>
    <string name="s3_title">Gotta Catch ‘Em All</string>
    <string name="s3_subtitle">We’re hoping if you’re reading this guide, you’re already logged into your Pokemon Go app and ready to start capturing Pokemon. While you’re looking at the map of your surrounding area, you’ll notice a small, white rectangle that ...</string>
    <string name="s4_title">Pokémon Go - server status, error messages, crashes and how to know the game is down</string>
    <string name="s4_subtitle">You can usually tell servers are offline with an explicit message along the lines of \'we are working to resolve the issue\', alongside a specific piece of cute Pokémon Go art work....</string>
    <string name="s5_title">What is the Poké Bal and how to catch Pokémon?</string>
    <string name="s5_subtitle">Once you\'ve gotten started with the game and captured your first Pokémon, it\'s time to go hunting for some others. You can find wild Pokémon by ...</string>
    <string name="s6_title">What is the Gym and How to join Gym and battle other players?</string>
    <string name="s6_subtitle">When you reach level five and visit a Gym, you\'ll be asked to join one of ...</string>
    <string name="s7_title">How to get Pikachu as your starter Pokémon?</string>
    <string name="s7_subtitle">1. Sign up for a Pokémon Go account. 2. Make your avatar. 3. When the Professor prompts you to ..</string>
    <string name="s8_title">How to get cool items from PokéStops (and explore the world around you, too)?</string>
    <string name="s8_subtitle">PokéStops are important or iconic places around your area: They may be special benches with dedication plaques, permanent art installations, or historic landmarks. They\'ll never be ...</string>
    <string name="s9_title">Here’s how to stop Pokémon Go from destroying your phone’s battery?</string>
    <string name="s9_subtitle">Our app has compiled a few tips that will help cut down on the amount of juice that Pokémon Go sucks down as you head out on the prowl for rare Pokémon...</string>
    <string name="s10_title">22 Helpful Pokémon Go Tips You Might Not Know Yet</string>
    <string name="s10_subtitle">1. Each pawprint on the Pokémon tracker represents about a 100-meter distance. 2. Your eggs won’t gain hatching progress if you travel faster than ...</string>
    <string name="s11_title">How To Get A Specific Eeveelution From Your Eevee?</string>
    <string name="s11_subtitle">Ever since launch, players have been wondering if you could actually control which Eeveelution you get, and now it appears we have a legitimate way....</string>
    <string name="s12_title">How to Win Battles?</string>
    <string name="s12_subtitle">Battles mostly come down to incessant tapping and landing your special attack. When it comes time to battle an opponent, there are only...</string>
    <string name="s13_title">How to increase Your Chances of Catching Pokémon, and Earn More XP?</string>
    <string name="s13_subtitle">It might seem easy at first, but catching pokémon gets harder as you level up. You start running into stronger pokémon, and your once-massive stash of...</string>
    <string name="s14_title">How to gain XP and level up faster in Pokemon Go!?</string>
    <string name="s14_subtitle">The leveling system in Pokemon Go is one of its central mechanics. There are so many things that are dependent on your...</string>
    <string name="share_title">Guides and tips for Pokemon Go - the best guides and tips for this game!</string>
    <string name="share_body"> You can find answer for this question there:</string>
    <string name="button_more">More</string>
    <string name="button_share">Share</string>
    <string name="s15_title">A Pokémon Go Tutorial</string>
    <string name="s15_subtitle">The game is about collecting Pokemon. In later stages of the game you...</string>
    <string name="AR_PlayStoreNotInstalled">No Play Store installed on device</string>
    <string name="AR_title">Rate </string>
    <string name="AR_message">If you enjoy using \"</string>
    <string name="AR_message1">\", please take a moment to rate it. Thanks for your support!</string>
    <string name="AR_rate">Rate it!</string>
    <string name="AR_later">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="AR_dismiss">No thanks</string>
</resources>
